MDUDUZI COMFORT MSIZA

CONTACT

Address: 6807 Drieziek 3 Orange Farm

South Africa 1841

Phone: 0766160815

Email: mducmsiza@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Time management
- Web design
- · Strategic partnership building
- · Exceptional time management
- Organised
- Good Communication
- · Good Team Player

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a self-motivated and highly skilled Information Technology student who is keen on applying academic foundation experience. Very punctual and organised individual with excellent interpersonal skills and the ability to communicate professionally. I am comfortable with working with different people from different backgrounds. I work well within a team and individually. Interested in an organization that will allow me to grow career wise while at the same time I am adding positive value to the organization.

WORK HISTORY

Web Developer (Part time), 03/2020 to Current **G-Media** - Vanderbijlpark, Gauteng

- Represented the team at meetings with executives, and discussed project goals and milestones.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement in a fast-paced environment.
- Converted mock-ups into HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON.

Winter School IT Support, 06/2019 to 07/2019 North West University - Vanderbijlpark, South Africa

 Managed the smooth operation of the winter school through preparation of the computers to make sure the worked smoothly and without any problems

Maths Class Assistant, 02/2018 to 06/2018

North West University - Vanderbijlpark, South Africa

• Worked directly with the NWU Maths Lecturer to help students who need help with certain aspects in and out of class

EDUCATION

National Senior Certificate: 11/2014

Mphethi Mahlatsi Secondary School - Orange Farm

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology, 04/2021

North West University - Vanderbijplark